## Taeyoung Yun

BLACK-BOX OPTIMIZATION · GENERATIVE MODELS

291 Daehark-ro, Yuseong-gu, Daejeon 34141

■ 99yty@kaist.ac.kr | 😭 dbsxodud-11.github.io | 🖸 dbsxodud-11 | 🞓 Taeyoung Yun

## Personal Profile

My research interest lies in solving complex and high-dimensional black-box optimization problems through the lens of conditional generative modeling. I'm currently interested in Diffusion Models, Generative Flow Networks, and their applications to real-world tasks, e.g., biological sequence design, material discovery, and mechanical design. I'm also interested in various decision making problems such as bandits, Reinforcement Learning and Multi-Agent RL.

## **Education**

### KAIST (Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology)

Daejeon, Korea

Ph.D in Industrial and Systems Engineering

March 2024 - Current

· Supervised by Jinkyoo Park

KAIST

Daejeon, Korea

M.S in Graduate School of AI September 2022 - February 2024

• Supervised by Jinkyoo Park

**KAIST** Daejeon, Korea

B.S in Industrial and Systems Engineering & Computer Science (Double Major)

March 2018 - August 2022

## **Experiences**

### Hong Kong University of Science and Technology (HKUST)

Hong kong

Visiting Intern

September 2024 - Current

• Internship at HKUST hosted by Ling Pan.

#### **Kakao Recommendation Team**

Seoul, Korea

Research Intern

March 2021 - August 2021

- Develop contextual bandit algorithms for a personal recommendation.
- Analyze the gap between simulation and real-world deployment.

## Projects \_\_\_\_\_

#### **Incentive Design for Managing Taxi Fleet**

Daejeon, Korea

Collaborate with ETRI

March 2023 - March 2024

#### **Traffic Light Optimization**

Seoul, Korea

Collaborate with KT

March 2022 - March 2023

## **Publications**

## **Guided Trajectory Generation with Diffusion Models for Offline Model-based Optimization**

Arxiv

**Taeyoung Yun**, Sujin Yun, Jaewoo Lee and Jinkyoo Park

2024

papercode

# An Offline Meta Black-box Optimization Framework for Adaptive Design of Urban Traffic Light Management Systems

KDD

<u>Taeyoung Yun\*</u>, Kanghoon Lee\*, Sujin Yun, Ilmyung Kim, Won-Woo Jung, Min-Cheol Kwon, Kyujin Choi, Yoohyeon Lee, and Jinkyoo Park (\*: Equal Contribution)

2024

paper

code

JULY 7, 2024

Learning to Scale Logits for Temperature-conditional GFlowNets  Minsu Kim*, Juhwan Ko*, Taeyoung Yun*, Dinghuai Zhang, Ling Pan, Woochang Kim, Jinkyoo Park, and Yoshua Bengio (*: Equal Contribution)  • paper  • code	ICML 2024
GTA: Generative Trajetory Augmentation with Guidance for Offline Reinforcement Learning  Jaewoo Lee*, Sujin Yun*, Taeyoung Yun, and Jinkyoo Park (*: Equal Contribution)  paper code	ICLR GenAI4DM Workshop (Spotlight) 2024
Local Search GFlowNets  Minsu Kim, Taeyoung Yun, Emmanuel Bengio, Dinghuai Zhang, Yoshua Bengio, Sungsoo Ahn, and Jinkyoo Park  • paper  • code	ICLR (Spotlight) 2024
Honors & Awards	
Dean's List (Top 2%) KAIST	2021
NH Big Data Competition (Excellence Award)  DACON	2021
Teaching Experiences	
Teaching Assistant IE437: Data-Driven Decision Making and Control	2023, 2024
<b>Teaching Assistant</b> MAS480: Introduction to Scientific Machine Learning	2022
Academic Services	
NIPS Reviewer	2024

JULY 7, 2024